Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The Barack Obama Quilt QSOS
    - Susan Shie oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-12-15 (Interview-id BOQ-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Written description of quilt, final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_003_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_003_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_003_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_003_04.wav
    - Bonnie Smith oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-12-15 (Interview-id BOQ-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_004_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_004_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_004_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_004_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_004_05.wav
    - Jeanette Thompson oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-12-16 (Interview-id BOQ-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_005_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_005_04.wav
    - Theresa Shellcroft oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-12-29 (Interview-id BOQ-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Brief autobiography/quilt description, final transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images), 1 color printout (from digital images)(3 images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_006_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_006_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_006_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_006_05.wav
    - Debra Gabel oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-09 (Interview-id BOQ-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_007_08.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_007_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_007_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_007_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_BOQ_007_04.wav; afc2007009_BOQ_007_06.wav
    - Edna Patterson-Petty oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-11 (Interview-id BOQ-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_008_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_008_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_008_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_008_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_008_04.wav
    - Sherry Shine oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-12 (Interview-id BOQ-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_009_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_009_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_009_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_009_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_009_04.wav
    - Wen Redmond oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-13 (Interview-id BOQ-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_010_07.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_010_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_010_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_BOQ_010_03.wav; afc2007009_BOQ_010_05.wav
    - Shawn Dubin oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-13 (Interview-id BOQ-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_011_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_011_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_011_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_011_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_011_04.wav
    - Connie Condrell oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-16 (Interview-id BOQ-012)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_012_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_012_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_012_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_012_04.wav
    - Carole Lyles Shaw oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-18 (Interview-id BOQ-013)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_013_01.wav
    - Valerie White oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-19 (Interview-id BOQ-014)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_BOQ_014_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_014_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_014_02.wav
    - Lisa Shepard Stewart oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-20 (Interview-id BOQ-015)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_015_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_015_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_015_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_015_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_015_04.wav
    - Jackie Campbell oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-21 (Interview-id BOQ-016)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_016_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_016_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_016_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_016_03.wav
    - Sherry Boram oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-23 (Interview-id BOQ-017)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_017_07.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_017_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_017_05.wav
    - Eileen Doughty oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-23 (Interview-id BOQ-018)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_018_07.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_018_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_018_05.wav
    - Catherine Lamkin oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-23 (Interview-id BOQ-019)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_019_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_019_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_019_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_019_02.wav
    - Cookie Washington oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-26 (Interview-id BOQ-020)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_BOQ_020_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_020_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_020_02.wav
    - Deb Cashatt oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-26 (Interview-id BOQ-021)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_021_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_021_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_021_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_021_03.wav
    - Kris Sazaki oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-26 (Interview-id BOQ-022)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_022_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_022_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_022_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_022_03.wav
    - Betty Colburn oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-26 (Interview-id BOQ-023)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_023_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_023_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_023_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_023_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_023_04.wav
    - Carolyn Crump oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-27 (Interview-id BOQ-024)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_024_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_024_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_024_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_024_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_024_04.wav
    - Stephanie Grissom oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-28 (Interview-id BOQ-025)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_025_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_025_03.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_025_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_025_01.wav
    - Sheila Kramer oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-29 (Interview-id BOQ-026)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_026_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_026_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_026_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_026_03.wav
    - Jayne Gaskins oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-01-30 (Interview-id BOQ-027)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_BOQ_027_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_027_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_027_02.wav
    - Jeanne Marklin oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-03 (Interview-id BOQ-028)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_028_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_028_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_028_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_028_04.wav
    - Carol Krueger oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-04 (Interview-id BOQ-029)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_029_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_029_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_029_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_029_03.wav
    - Asake Denise Foye Jones oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-04 (Interview-id BOQ-030)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_030_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_030_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_030_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_030_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_030_05.wav
    - Elizabeth Warner oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-06 (Interview-id BOQ-031)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_031_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_031_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_031_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_031_03.wav
    - Joy-Lily oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-06 (Interview-id BOQ-032)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_BOQ_032_01.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_032_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_BOQ_032_03.wav; afc2007009_BOQ_032_05.wav
    - Sandra Hankins oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-11 (Interview-id BOQ-033)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_033_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_033_03.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_033_04.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_033_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_033_01.wav
    - Suanne Reed oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-11 (Interview-id BOQ-034)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital documents, 4 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_034_07.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_034_08.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_034_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_034_05.wav
    - Michelle Flamer oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-11 (Interview-id BOQ-035)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images), 4 3x5 color prints; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_035_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_035_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_035_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_035_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_035_04.wav
    - Peg Keeney oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-12 (Interview-id BOQ-036)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_036_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_036_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_036_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_036_04.wav
    - Charlene Hughes oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-12 (Interview-id BOQ-037)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, accompanying written description of quilt, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_037_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_037_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_037_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_037_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_037_05.wav
    - Maria Shell oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-18 (Interview-id BOQ-038)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images), 2 3x5 color prints; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_038_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_038_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_038_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_038_04.wav
    - Vivian Milholen oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-19 (Interview-id BOQ-039)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_039_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_039_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_039_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_039_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_039_05.wav
    - Carol Beck oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-20 (Interview-id BOQ-040)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_040_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_040_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_040_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_040_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_040_05.wav
    - Adriene Cruz oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-23 (Interview-id BOQ-041)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_041_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_041_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_041_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_041_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_041_05.wav
    - Sauda Zahra oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-25 (Interview-id BOQ-042)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_042_04.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_042_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_042_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_042_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_042_01.wav
    - Ann Anastastio oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-26 (Interview-id BOQ-043)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_043_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_043_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_043_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_043_03.wav
    - Marjorie Diggs Freeman oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-04 (Interview-id BOQ-044)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, accompanying written description of quilt, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_044_12.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_044_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_044_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_044_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 4 digital recordings; afc2007009_BOQ_044_04-11.wav
    - Marlene O'Bryant-Seabrook oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-06 (Interview-id BOQ-045)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_045_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_045_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_045_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_045_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_045_04.wav
    - Chris Gilman oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-09 (Interview-id BOQ-046)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_046_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_046_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_046_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_046_03.wav
    - Lavialle Campbell oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-09 (Interview-id BOQ-047)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_047_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_047_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_047_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_047_04.wav
    - Ellaree Pray oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-11 (Interview-id BOQ-048)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_048_06.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_048_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_048_02.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_048_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_048_04.wav
    - Martha Gilbert oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-16 (Interview-id BOQ-049)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_049_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_049_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_049_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_049_03.wav
    - Louisa L. Smith oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-26 (Interview-id BOQ-050)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, two copies artist statement, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_050_05.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_050_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_050_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_050_03.wav
    - Karla Schreffer oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-06-02 (Interview-id BOQ-051)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_BOQ_051_03.doc; afc2007009_BOQ_051_01.jpg; afc2007009_BOQ_051_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_BOQ_051_04.wav
  - The California QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in California.
    - Bonita Morley oral history interview conducted by Amy Henderson, 2001-05-31 (Interview-id CA-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR227
    - Joan Schulze oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2003-08-04 (Interview-id CA94107-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR228; AFC 2007/009: SR229
    - Suzan Friedland oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2010-12-03 (Interview-id CA94118-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA94118_001_06.doc; afc2007009_CA94118_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA94118_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA94118_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_CA94118_001_04.wav
    - Sonya Lee Barrington oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2008-02-19 (Interview-id CA94121-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA94121_001_03.doc; afc2007009_CA94121_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA94121_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR553
    - Linda MacDonald oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2008-02-19 (Interview-id CA94121-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA94121_002_03.doc; afc2007009_CA94121_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA94121_002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR554
    - Joe Cunningham oral history interview conducted by Janneken Smucker, 2007-08-18 (Interview-id CA94129-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_CA94129_001_01.doc; afc2007009_CA94129_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_CA94129_001_02.mp3
    - Sherri Lynn Wood oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-03-07 (Interview-id CA94130-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA94130_001_05.doc; afc2007009_CA94130_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA94130_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_CA94130_001_03.wav
    - Judith Content oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2008-02-18 (Interview-id CA94306-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA94306_001_03.doc; afc2007009_CA94306_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA94306_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR627; AFC 2007/009: SR628
    - Liz Berg oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-04-27 (Interview-id CA94546-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Linda Schmidt oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-06-07 (Interview-id CA94568-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Susan Else oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-04-30 (Interview-id CA95060-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA95060_001_04.doc; afc2007009_CA95060_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95060_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95060_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_CA95060_001_05.wav
    - Vicky Groom oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-09 (Interview-id CA95482-01)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95482_01_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95482_01_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95482_01_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR528
    - Leila Kazimi oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-09 (Interview-id CA95482-03)